# LOGAN ALLEN

(770) 503-5494 loganallc@gmail.com

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

# **Co-founder, Software Developer**

## **Slingput**

August 2014 - Current

- Developed a web app for testing demand and creating beautiful landing pages using Ruby on Rails.
- Ranked among the top five new startups on the front page of ProductHunt (9/8/14).

## **Software Development Intern**

## **Gather Technologies**

June 2014 - Current

- Rewrote private events management web app for restaurants in AngularJS.
- Redesigned marketing site, implemented responsive design for mobile, and improved SEO.
- Wrote automated testing suite using Karma and Protractor.

#### **Software Development Intern**

#### **TripLingo**

January - May 2014

 Reimagined TripLingo's app through JavaScript and Appcelerator Titanium for translation in an emergency room context.

## Front-end Development Intern

## **BestFit Mobile**

April - December 2013

- Led front-end development to create an app that allows doctors to refer patients to other doctors for Fresenius Medical Care, a company with 55,000 employees.
- Developed a conference room booking app using **Sencha Touch** for internal use.

# SIDE PROJECTS

- Autoscope (September 2014). Created a third person view of reality using an Oculus Rift and a Parrot Drone at MHacks. Won the **Best Under 20 Prize** presented by the Thiel Foundation. JavaScript.
- **Docket App** (April 2014). Created a web app for presenting upcoming events that integrated with Google Calendar. Featured in Access North Georgia and the Gainesville Times. JavaScript.
- Clerk App (Fall 2013). Android news app that allowed users to directly reward authors for quality articles through micro-donations. Java, NodeJS.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Atlanta, GA

# **Georgia Institute of Technology**

Fall 2014 - Current

Computer Science major - Graduating May 2018 (Expected)

#### Skills

JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS, Design, Prototyping, SH, SQL, Python, Ruby on Rails, Testing

#### Bio

Design-oriented by nature, I focus on front-end development and user experience, leveraging my passion for the open web to craft beautiful web apps and sites.

A builder at heart, I am a self-starter whose passion shows in everything I do. I love diving into new technologies and am able to quickly familiarize myself with large codebases to begin contributing.